<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name= "Games">
        <item>Metro 2033</item>
        <item>Metro Last Light</item>
        <item>Metro 2033 Redux</item>
        <item>Metro Last Light Redux</item>
        <item>Metro Exodus</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string name= "Metro_2033">
        "Metro 2033 is a Post-Apocalyptic Survival-Horror and First Person Shooter video game based on the novel of the same name, Metro 2033, by Russian author Dmitry Glukhovsky. The Ukrainian developing company, 4A Games, and former publishers of the series THQ collaborated with Dmitry Glukhovsky to create a digital rendition of his novel for the Xbox 360 and PC platforms. Originally, the game was to be released with the subtitle: The Last Refuge, but the subtitle was later dropped. A sequel, Metro Last Light, was released in 2013."
    </string>
    <string name= "MetroLL">
        "Metro: Last Light (formerly known as Metro 2034, often abbreviated as Last Light) is a post-apocalyptic first-person shooter and sequel to Metro 2033 developed by 4A Games and published by Deep Silver. Last Light was followed by a third addition to the Metro video game series, Metro Exodus, which was released in 2019."
    </string>
    <string name= "Metro_2033_Redux">
        "Metro Redux is a post-apocalyptic first-person shooter, and a two-part remake of Metro 2033 and Metro: Last Light for the PS4 and X-One consoles. It was developed by 4A Games and published by Deep Sliver. The enhanced versions of both games can be bought together as a bundle or separately. Metro Redux features remakes of both games in an improved 4A Engine. While Metro Last Light Redux includes general improvements, Metro 2033 Redux has been completely remade in the Last Light engine and updated to include the same features as Metro: Last Light. Metro Redux has been released for the PS4 and the Xbox One, as well as PC, in August 2014. Almost six years later it was made available on the Nintendo Switch in February 2020."
    </string>
    <string name= "Metro_LL_Redux">
        "Metro: Last Light Redux is the updated version of Metro Last Light for the PC and new platforms - featuring improved graphics and lighting. It is part of the two-part remake Metro Redux."
    </string>
    <string name= "Metro_Exodus">
        "Metro Exodus (Russian: Метро: Исход) is the third part in the Metro video game series, set after the events of Metro: Last Light and Metro 2035. It follows the adventures of Artyom, who returns to reprise his role as the protagonist of the game. Exodus is a story-driven first-person shooter from 4A Games that blends deadly combat and stealth with exploration and survival horror. It features a mixture of confined corridors and vast, non-linear levels (set in the Russian wilderness), tying up together to follow a storyline that spans an entire year through all four seasons. Inspired by the novels of Dmitry Glukhovsky, Metro Exodus is the first game to be set completely after the books rather than during or between them. It continues Artyom's story from where Metro 2035 left off."
    </string>
    <string name="AboutDev">
       "Protsenko Danil SMB-701-O"
    </string>
</resources>